http://klcs.org/privacy-policy/

KLCS at Home Learning Live
Nothing is more important to KLCS than protecting the private information of visitors to our site. Below you’ll find information about our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your and your children’s personally identifiable information (such as your full name, address, email address, telephone number and/or other identifying information) and preserving the integrity of the medium.
Please read the following carefully. If you have any questions or concerns, please send us an email at info@klcs.pbs.org.
Gathering and Use of Information
KLCS will never willfully disclose any personally identifiable information about our online audience to any third party without first receiving the user’s permission. We do not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors other than what is supplied to us on a voluntary basis.
Visitors to the KLCS Web Site may voluntarily supply certain personally identifiable information in connection with (i) contest or sweepstakes registration, (ii) subscription registration for sites or services which require subscription (such as email newsletters), (iii) requests for membership information and (iv) e-commerce transactions. In addition, personally identifiable information is voluntarily provided in connection with certain content submissions, community postings (i.e., forums or bulletin boards), comments and suggestions, or voting.
KLCS may use such information only for conducting the activities stated above, and for internal marketing and promotional purposes. KLCS does not make mailing lists available to other organizations or third parties. The extent of such use is Lexington Steele fucking hard big tittied blonde pornstar – big, pussy, hardcorealways explained at the time a site visitor provides such information. If the visitor does not want this information collected and used by us for the disclosed internal purposes, the visitor is given an opportunity to “opt-out.” Our visitors need to recognize, however, that under certain circumstances, if they select to “opt-out” they may not be eligible for certain activities for which the personally identifiable information is needed. (For example, if a contest participant elects to “opt-out” on permitting us to collect and use their personal information, we cannot contact them if they win without using such information.) best casino sites
Acceptance of these KLCS Web Site Privacy Policy Terms and Conditions
By using this site, you signify your agreement to the freepornvideosterms and conditions of this KLCS Web Site Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the KLCS Web Site following the posting of any changes to these terms shall mean that you have accepted those changes. If you have any questions or concerns, please email us at info@klcs.pbs.org.
SUPPORT
KLCS ON FACEBOOK
KLCS VIEWER MAGAZINE
© 2020 Copyright KLCS. All rights reserved. | Site by Apple7Media.com
